

Saurav Pampatwar

Software Engineer

Enthusiastic Software Engineer with a flair of creating elegant solutions in the least amount of time. Having in-depth knowledge of Java and React technology and experience of more than 2 years in the software industry. Organized and self-motivated software engineer which follows all software development phases in software development lifecycle. Utilises superior communication skills to build meaningful, trusting relationships that exceed client demands.

sauravpampatwar7@gmail.com

+91 9730251658

Nanded, India

github.com/Sauravp123

in linkedin.com/in/saurav-pampatwar

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer GlobalLogic

08/2021 - Present Pune, India

Currently working on the Analysis and Financial Planning project with the tech stack Java, Reactis and Javascript. Build the Features like New Modelling Experience for the users to easily create any type of models related to planning. Integrated third-party applications into existing software, enhancing features and performance.Run the CI and CD pipeline to test the software and also used the Github commands to create Merge Request and Pull Request. Also, worked on the Jenkins pipeline to make sure code passes with all checks.Worked on the B2B E-Commerce project, to develop the features in project like Discounts, Promotions and Shipping etc. Writing the clean code using Java, Reactjs and performing unit and component testing using JUnit and Mockito.Wrote clean and dynamic code, leveraging expertise across multiple programming languages to meet diverse requirements.Enhanced software development by using working knowledge of Agile frameworks.

Application Specialist Centiro Solutions

06/2021 - 07/2021 Pune, India

Worked on the SAAS based application in which, I was to manage the Carriers and Receivers data. Also, To create different kinds of carriers on the application and create the various services for that carriers like express parcels, domestic delivery, Integrated E-commerce loaistics.

EDUCATION

Bachelor Of Technology(B.Tech)

Shri Guru Gobind Singhji Institute Of Engineering and Technology

08/2017 - 07/2021 Nanded, India

12th

Blue Bells Junior College

06/2016 - 07/2017 Nanded, India

10th

Pratibha Niketan High School

03/2014 - 04/2015 Nanded, India

SKILLS

HTML/CSS

Design and development

Web application development

Agile Development

ACHIEVEMENTS

Victor Of The Week

Awarded due to phenomenal performace during recent sprints and also put all possible efforts to make it success. Always keen to learn new things and ramping up very quickly,

LANGUAGES

English

Full Professional Proficiency

Full Professional Proficiency

Marathi

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

CERTIFICATIONS

Programming for Everybody (Getting Started with Python):- Coursera

Data Science Bootcamp: - Dphi

Certificate of Participation in Flip the Script Challenge :- Unstop